Danger Is Rising!
Megalodon is a action, science fiction, horror film directed by James Thomas.
A military vessel on the search for an unidentified submersible finds themselves face to face with a giant
shark, forced to use only what they have on board to defend themselves from the monstrous beast.
Admiral King, played by Michael Madsen.
Jameson, played by Scott C. Roe.
Captain Ivanov, played by Ego Mikitas.
Cheng, played by Paulina Nguyen.
Captain Streeper, played by Dominic Pace.
Yana Popov, played by Aimee Stolte.
The Asylum is an American independent film company and distributor that
focuses on producing low-budget, direct-to-video films.
The company has produced titles that capitalize on productions by major studios, often using film titles
and scripts very similar to those of current blockbusters in order to lure customers.
These titles have been dubbed "mockbusters" by the press.
The film explores themes of monster, submarine, shark
attack, prehistoric creature, creature.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.